genie-soft.com 2011-12-31

# Genie9: Company |Privacy statement| Offers a Wide Range of Backup, Restore, Disaster Recovery and Online Backup Solutions

  |  |     
  |  |     
|  |   
---  
|  | 

## Privacy Statement  
  
---  
   
Genie9 has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of the users of our website and online service. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our users.   
   
**What this Privacy Statement Covers**  

  * This privacy statement covers treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Genie9 through a website owned and operated by Genie9. 
  * This privacy statement does not apply to the practices of companies that Genie9 does not own or control, or of persons that Genie9 does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Genie9's websites link. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  

  * You can visit the websites of Genie9 without revealing any personal information. However, Genie9 needs certain personal information if you wish to register for a members account, receive a Genie9 newsletter, purchase a product, or use certain Genie9 services. 
  * Where required, this information may include your company contact information and your personal contact information. Genie9 will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to set up your account, to provide you with requested services, and to contact you regarding new services. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * Genie9 will not share any information with anyone else and will remain confidential unless requested explicit permission from users to share information. 

Changes to this Privacy Statement   

  * Genie9 may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this statement from time to time. Please review this statement periodically. Your continued use of Genie9 services after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

### **Stay informed**  
  
Subscribe to our **"What's New?"** newsletter and get all the latest updates about our products, new releases and offers. 

Subscribe Now  

  |  |     
  |  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
**Our Clients:** |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
 |   |  |   |  |   |  |   |  |   |   
  |   |    |   |    |   |    |   |    |   |    

---  
Home Products |  Business Products |  Store |  Partners |  Support |  Company  
  
Genie Timeline Home  
Genie Backup Manager Home  
Genie Mail Backup  
Genie Archive for Outlook  
Genie Timeline Free  
Outlook Express Backup

|     
Genie Timeline Professional  
 Genie Timeline Business  
 Genie Timeline Server  
Genie Backup Manager Professional   
Genie Backup Manager Server  

Individual  
Small and Medium Business  
Enterprise  
Education  
Health care

|     
Genie9 Store   
Genie Offers    
Upgrade  
Volume Discounts  
Educational Discounts  
Our Guarantee  
Awards  
Reviews & Testimonials |    
Resellers  
Web Affiliates  
OEM  
Service Providers    
Our Partners  
FAQs  
Knowledge Base  
Tutorials & Manuals  
Contact Sales  
Demos |    
About Genie9  
Genie News  
Newsletter  
Our Customers  
Privacy Statement  
Legal Notices  
Careers  
Contact Us  
Site Map  
   
  |    |
